https://www.summitsports.com/privacy-policy.html

star-icon
You are using a web browser we don't support. Please use the latest version of one of these browsers
Privacy & Security | Privacy Policy
This privacy policy explains how SummitSports.com collects, uses, and discloses the information of users of the SummitSports.com  Web site (the "SummitSports.com Web site," or "our Web site").
Important terms
When reviewing any privacy policy on the Internet, you should be familiar with the terms "personally identifiable information" and "aggregate information." "Personally identifiable information" is any information that can be used to identify, contact, or locate you as an individual. Common examples are your name and email address.
"Aggregate information" lumps your behavior or characteristics together with those of a group. For instance, we may let advertisers know that 50% of our users are over 35 without disclosing the personal information of any one individual.
Collecting your information
When you register for the SummitSports.com Web site we collect personally identifiable information, including (but not limited to) your name, physical address, email address, phone numbers, and billing information. All of this information is mandatory; without it we will not register you. We also collect personally identifiable information through purchase forms, surveys, sweepstakes entries, emails we receive from you, and your other interactions with our Web site.
When you use our Web site we may collect a variety of technical data, which we store in both aggregate and, if you are registered with SummitSports.com, personally identifiable forms. This data includes (but is not limited to) your IP address (a unique number that identifies your access account on the Internet), domain, and Web browser information. We may track the page you visited before coming to the SummitSports.com Web site, and the page you link to when you leave the SummitSports.com Web site, which of our pages you access, and how long you spend on each page.
The SummitSports.com Web site uses "cookies," which are small pieces of information stored on your computer. Cookies let our Web site recognize previous visitors to our web page, record a visitor's progress from page to page, and recall certain information a visitor entered previously. For instance, a cookie may store your password, or note that you're interested in electronics. You can choose to decline our cookies (e.g., by setting your browser to reject cookies), but if you do, some parts of the SummitSports.com web site may not operate properly. We may also use tracking images and applets to collect the same information.
We may use third-party advertising companies to serve ads on our behalf. These companies may employ cookies and action tags (also known as single pixel gifs or web beacons) to measure advertising effectiveness. Any information that these third parties collect via cookies and action tags is completely anonymous. We allow third parties to collect aggregate and other anonymous information about our visitors through the SummitSports.com Web site. Should we enter into agreements that allow third parties to collect personally identifiable information about our visitors, we will inform visitors of these activities at the location of the collection. Finally, note that our Web site may or may not contains links to other sites on the Internet. Please remember that if you click on one of these links, you are leaving our Web site and entering another. Again, we are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of these other web sites, and encourage you to read their privacy statements (which may differ from ours).
Using Your Information
This section describes how we use and disclose the information we collect.
We use aggregate information about your behavior and equipment to improve the performance of our Web site, and to evaluate your reaction to the content and design of our Web site. We may use personally identifiable information to customize the content and layout of our Web site's pages for you, to store your SummitSports.com account information, to record SummitSports.com Web site session information (such as items you have added to your shopping cart) order status, and to store your purchase history.
We also use personally identifiable and aggregate information for a variety of marketing and promotional purposes. For instance, we use what we have learned about your preferences to alert you to new areas when you return to our Web site, or to help us or our business partners target advertising or product placements to your particular interests.
From time to time we will send you emails related to the SummitSports.com Web site. At various points during your visits to SummitSports.com, you are provided opportunities to indicate an interest in receiving email about special offers and other promotional information. If you do not wish to receive special offers and promotional information emails from us, please let us know by unchecking the "email notification" request box on the SummitSports.com Web site. You may also opt out of this promotional email list after you have registered by contacting us, or by following the "opt out" instructions that may be included in the emails you receive.
If you supply us with your telephone numbers, you will only receive telephone contact from us regarding your SummitSports.com Web site account, or orders you have placed online. We will not share your telephone number with other organizations.
Google
Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our site. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our users based on their visit to our site and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.
We have implemented the following:
Remarketing with or without AdSense
Demographics and Interests Reporting
We along with third-party vendors, such as Google use first-party cookies (such as the Google Analytics cookies) and third-party cookies (such as the DoubleClick cookie) or other third-party identifiers together to compile data regarding user interactions with ad impressions, and other ad service functions as they relate to our website.
Opting out: Users can set preferences for how Google advertises to you using the Google Ad Settings page. Alternatively, you can opt out by visiting the Network Advertising initiative opt out page or permanently using the Google Analytics Opt Out Browser add on.
Security
Any SummitSports.com Web site accounts you may have are password-protected. We recommend that you do not divulge your password to anyone. We will never ask you for your password in an unsolicited phone call or in an unsolicited email.
We have instituted security measures in our physical facilities to protect against the loss, misuse or alteration of information that we have collected from you. In addition, we always use industry-standard encryption technologies when transferring and receiving customer data exchanged with our Web site. We've also implemented industry standard security measures for our ISP.
Please keep in mind, however, that no data transmission over the Internet or any wireless network can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, we cannot guarantee the security of any information you transmit using our Web site, and you transmit such information at your own risk. SummitSports.com further does not assume responsibility for use or disclosure of your information that are the result of unauthorized or illegal access to our systems or those of our vendors or partners.
Contact information
Inquiries and requests relating to the SummitSports.com Web site policy should be sent by email to help@SummitSports.com. You can also reach us at our mailing address:
SummitSports.com Privacy Policy & Customer Service SummitSports.com
330 Enterprise Court
Bloomfield Hills, MI.
48302
Policy changes
From time to time, we may use customer information for new, unanticipated uses not previously disclosed in our privacy notice. If we make such a change, we will post a notice on the SummitSports.com Web site. If you are concerned about how your information is used, please check our Web site periodically to review our current privacy policy.
SideArrow
Don’t Miss Out!
Get exclusive email sneak peeks and the latest on upcoming
sales, exclusive offers and events. Plus we’ll throw in a special
perk, just for signing up.*
* Offer valid for first-time registrants only.
Submit
